‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪I think
‪I really want to…
‪get engaged to you.
‪Will you
‪be my fiancé?
‪My goodness.
‪My gosh.
‪You managed to make time to come.
‪Ma'am.
‪I'm so glad you could come.
‪I reserved you a seat, just in case.
‪The ceremony will start soon.
‪Let's go inside.
‪Oh, no.
‪Not only am I not family,
‪but I also know
‪Chairwoman Baek quite well.
‪If I were to suddenly show up
‪without notice,
‪she'll be taken aback.
‪I'll just do what I've always done
‪and watch from afar.
‪Yes, of course.
‪Do whatever makes you feel comfortable.
‪-Go on inside.
‪-I will.
‪-You'll stay? Then we'll talk later.
‪-Yes, don't worry.
‪EPISODE 9
‪…two, three.
‪-Congratulations!
‪I wish you both happiness.
‪What a nice day.
‪Congratulations, Mother.
‪I did it.
‪I'll take some photos now.
‪-Ma'am, Mr. Ma, big smiles.
‪-Okay.
‪One, two, three.
‪Make an arch with your arms.
‪One arm each from both sides.
‪One, two, three.
‪Yes, wonderful. There we go.
‪Chairwoman, please join them.
‪And you too, ma'am.
‪Thank you for raising me well.
‪-What are you doing?
‪-What's gotten into him?
‪That's lovely. Look over here, please.
‪One, two, three.
‪Ma'am, you look a bit tense.
‪-Let's see a big smile.
‪-Okay.
‪-Big smile.
‪-Sure.
‪-No need to be nervous.
‪-Right.
‪Clench your fists a few times to relax.
‪ELDEST SON
‪How are you, son?
‪I'm fine.
‪Your flight to Korea…
‪I'll return soon,
‪as soon as my business here is done.
‪Then…
‪you're still in the US?
‪Yes.
‪I'll call when I get back.
‪-Can you make an arch?
‪-An arch?
‪Just like that.
‪-Round and round
‪Round and round
‪-I think that'll do.
‪-Mr. Bong.
‪Stand closer to each other.
‪-It's lovely here.
‪-Isn't it?
‪You have no idea how much effort I put
‪into finding this place
‪to celebrate our engagement.
‪Yeo-ri, they call this
‪the bridge that reflects the moon.
‪The bridge that reflects the moon?
‪Yes. Look over there.
‪There are moons floating on the water.
‪Oh, you're right.
‪The day I held your hand,
‪the moon was also shining brightly.
‪Do you remember?
‪Of course I remember.
‪When you saw ghosts for a full month,
‪it was tough, wasn't it?
‪No.
‪It wasn't tough at all, thanks to you.
‪I was actually grateful to the ghosts
‪because they brought me to you.
‪I mean it.
‪Wow, it's so pretty.
‪-Yeo-ri.
‪-Yes?
‪Today's a special day.
‪Is there anything you want to do?
‪I'm doing it right now.
‪Strolling with the man I like.
‪It would be nicer
‪if we could hold hands too, but still.
‪We can.
‪Not tonight,
‪but someday.
‪That day will definitely come.
‪We promised
‪to find a solution together, remember?
‪Then I'll need to recover
‪my memories first.
‪I just can't remember.
‪I must be too afraid
‪to face whatever happened.
‪We'll take our time
‪and do things one by one.
‪I'm right by your side.
‪And now that we're really engaged,
‪let's promise to tell each other
‪if anything's burdening us.
‪Okay?
‪Okay.
‪-It's really pretty.
‪-Yeah.
‪What was my mother doing there?
‪She headed straight to Reina Hotel
‪as soon as she landed.
‪Not even the secretaries knew
‪why she returned to Korea
‪ahead of schedule.
‪Find out why she came back
‪Yes, sir. Will do.
‪I can always create new circumstances.
‪When that time comes,
‪the stake you hold could be of great help.
‪Have Director Gong give her a call
‪so that Director Ok can get prepared.
‪Yes, sir.
‪Mom, how long do we have to wait?
‪Siena Hall's at the center of attention
‪since Yeo-ri's engagement.
‪How do you know that?
‪Is there a response already?
‪I checked, of course.
‪Siena Hall's booked through to next year,
‪and everyone's talking about
‪Yeo-ri's dress and makeup.
‪Mom.
‪Shouldn't we shut this down
‪before the synergy gets out of hand?
‪You have a point.
‪If she gains momentum
‪from stronger profits and performance,
‪we'll be at a disadvantage.
‪Exactly.
‪What do we do then?
‪What do you think?
‪Use that brain of yours for once.
‪I am using my brain.
‪You never think.
‪You never use your brain,
‪-so I always have to--
‪-She wants us to be quiet.
‪Hello, Director Gong.
‪Pardon?
‪Oh, my.
‪I didn't think
‪you'd make a decision so quickly.
‪Thank you so much.
‪Yes.
‪I promise you won't be disappointed.
‪Thank you again.
‪Yes, of course.
‪Goodbye then. Thank you.
‪What did he say?
‪Is Director Gong going to side with us?
‪Yeah.
‪If he's with us, does that mean
‪the other directors are in too?
‪You bet.
‪When will they start?
‪It's best to attack
‪when the enemy least expects it,
‪so right away.
‪Right now?
‪This is Ok Gye-hui.
‪Let's call an extraordinary
‪shareholders' meeting.
‪The agenda is
‪the removal of Cheon Yeo-ri,
‪CEO of Reina Hotel.
‪She isn't picking up.
‪Ok Gye-hui knows no fear.
‪I'm sorry.
‪It ended up coming to this.
‪No, I let my guard down too.
‪Who knew she'd strike
‪the day after your engagement ceremony?
‪How are things looking?
‪Those loyal to the former chairman
‪have sided with Director Ok,
‪putting us 3% behind in shares.
‪In the end, it'll most likely come down
‪to a 51 to 49 split.
‪How about
‪using the slush fund information
‪you obtained recently?
‪I've obtained information
‪that they amassed a slush fund
‪by purchasing artworks
‪to display in the hotel.
‪Yeeon Museum of Art is involved,
‪and so is Ha-ri's uncle,
‪Chief Prosecutor Ok Gye-dong.
‪That would work to our advantage.
‪Why not release it now?
‪Everything is still circumstantial.
‪We don't have anyone's confession
‪or proof to back the claim.
‪If we release it rashly
‪at a critical time like this,
‪we'll struggle to maintain
‪our stock price.
‪And with Chief Prosecutor
‪Ok Gye-dong on their side,
‪things could go badly
‪and the hotel and I could become targets.
‪I do remember something similar happened
‪during the former chairman's time.
‪The truth will eventually come out,
‪but it will take a long time.
‪In the meantime,
‪Reina and I'll be dragged through the mud.
‪Time isn't on our side.
‪I'll request an investigation
‪when the time is right.
‪Are there any shareholders
‪worth contacting?
‪Here's the list.
‪Let's contact as many as we can.
‪You'll do it yourself, ma'am?
‪I have to do whatever it takes.
‪Hello.
‪This is Cheon Yeo-ri, CEO of Reina.
‪How have you been?
‪Hello, Chairman. It's Baek Gyeong-ja.
‪Yes, I know.
‪I should've kept them in line
‪while I could.
‪I heard your child is clever and bright.
‪I hope they learn a great deal
‪and join our company.
‪Hi, Gang-uk.
‪Something came up at work.
‪Can I call you once things are settled?
‪Yes, of course.
‪Call me when you have time.
‪Thanks.
‪They're waiting for you inside.
‪Hello. Sorry for the delay.
‪Shall we sit down?
‪You've seen it once before,
‪how CEO Cheon's personal life
‪dragged down the stock price.
‪Let's drink.
‪-Do give us your full support.
‪-Gosh.
‪Don't worry, Chairwoman.
‪-Everything will work out.
‪-Thank you.
‪I'm sure you see
‪that she has her shortcomings,
‪so I hope you'll…
‪No. Even so, sir--
‪Come in.
‪Ma'am?
‪Here's the information
‪you requested yesterday.
‪-Mr. Bong.
‪-Yes?
‪I'd like to contact her,
‪Han Se-in, in person.
‪Yes, ma'am.
‪Min-hwan.
‪You're here.
‪What's the occasion,
‪asking me to keep you company?
‪You mind?
‪Of course I don't.
‪You're surrounded by people.
‪I'm surprised, that's all.
‪You ignored so many of my calls until now.
‪Sorry.
‪I had a lot to sort out.
‪So? Did you sort everything out?
‪Almost.
‪Does that include Yeo-ri?
‪She must be having a tough time.
‪She is in a tough situation,
‪but I doubt things are bad for her.
‪Look at her.
‪Despite everything,
‪she quashed those rumors
‪and got engaged to that prosecutor.
‪I do admire her resilience.
‪How are you doing?
‪Let's drink.
‪You don't leave any openings, do you?
‪Neither do I.
‪Min-hwan.
‪If I were to replace Yeo-ri,
‪would you date me?
‪Yeo-ri will lose her position
‪after the shareholders' meeting.
‪It won't be as easy as you think.
‪She's Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪Be honest with me.
‪Is it that impossible to give up on her?
‪When did it all begin?
‪I'm not sure.
‪Ever since I was young,
‪I've always worried
‪about other people's feelings.
‪But with Yeo-ri…
‪I didn't have to do that,
‪and I could relax around her.
‪That's why I grew to like her.
‪I thought she'd always stay
‪right where she was.
‪But when I came back…
‪Before I give up for good…
‪It may seem reckless,
‪but I might try something different.
‪It'll be my first and last attempt.
‪Ma'am, it's a call regarding Ms. Han.
‪Hello, Cheon Yeo-ri speaking.
‪She's out of the country?
‪Then where is she?
‪Yes.
‪Okay.
‪Is that so?
‪You can reach her by phone though, right?
‪Put me through
‪once you're able to reach her.
‪Thanks.
‪Gang-uk.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪I tried to be patient and wait,
‪but I couldn't reach you
‪when we'd just gotten engaged.
‪And I missed you.
‪I was also worried
‪that something was wrong.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪Did I do something wrong?
‪Is that what you were worried about?
‪I'm sorry. I should've called you.
‪What's going on?
‪It's not in the news yet,
‪but an extraordinary shareholders' meeting
‪will be held at Reina soon.
‪The main agenda will be my removal.
‪That's why things were a bit crazy.
‪Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
‪I thought our engagement
‪helped secure your position.
‪Is it a serious situation?
‪I'm trying my best
‪to persuade the shareholders,
‪but things don't look great.
‪It looks like I might have to
‪stay here all night.
‪I'll stay with you.
‪No. You can't do that.
‪Why not? I belong right by your side.
‪If there's not much I can do,
‪I'll run coffee errands.
‪I make pretty good coffee.
‪CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‪FRIENDLY, HOSTILE, NEUTRAL
‪Yeo-ri. You can take your gloves off
‪when you're with me.
‪I'll be careful.
‪Okay.
‪Who is this person that you're so…
‪REINA HOLDINGS
‪MAJOR SHAREHOLDERS CHECKLIST
‪CKO Construction is one of
‪Reina Holdings' major shareholders.
‪One of the chairman's sons got divorced
‪and the former daughter-in-law
‪received some shares.
‪-That's Han Se-in?
‪-Yeah.
‪So I'm gathering information
‪to find a way to win her over.
‪Her father is Han Jeong-eup.
‪I heard that name somewhere.
‪Do you know Chaeum Artrion?
‪He built that.
‪I know. My mom took me there
‪to see shows when I was young.
‪As an adult,
‪I went a few times with my grandma.
‪She must have
‪a lot of memories there with you.
‪Of course. She loved going there.
‪Since CKO Construction is owned
‪by her former in-laws,
‪I'm hoping Ms. Han
‪will make a different vote.
‪So I'm waiting to hear from her.
‪Ma'am!
‪Ma'am.
‪I didn't see anything.
‪But that's not what's important.
‪Ms. Han is currently residing
‪in Singapore.
‪What?
‪She runs her own business there
‪and actively holds exhibitions too.
‪What kind of exhibitions do you mean?
‪Well, I heard…
‪She's an art director
‪or something of the kind.
‪It's all here.
‪Her name is also on the list of attendees
‪of the hotel investment conference
‪that you held off on attending.
‪Is that so?
‪Put me through to her
‪as soon as you reach her.
‪Yes, will do.
‪I'll see myself out then.
‪She seems to be closely aligned
‪with our interests.
‪I think we've got a good shot.
‪Ma'am, I'm coming in!
‪I'm sorry, ma'am.
‪We got a call from Ms. Han.
‪Hello.
‪This is Cheon Yeo-ri of Reina.
‪I'm going abroad on a business trip.
‪I understand that it's a conference
‪to attract investors,
‪but why go now
‪if it won't bring immediate results?
‪Are you confident you can manage?
‪Yes.
‪Please keep up the work on your end.
‪I'll stay in touch
‪with any shareholders I can reach,
‪even while I'm abroad.
‪Will you be able to return on time?
‪Of course.
‪Yeo-ri's going abroad for business
‪at a time like this?
‪I got an invitation to it too.
‪It is a pretty large-scale conference
‪as far as attracting investment goes.
‪I get why she wants to go,
‪but why go now at a time like this?
‪Yeo-ri must feel cornered
‪to resort to something this ridiculous.
‪She'd likely lose her position
‪if the vote were tomorrow.
‪Even if she makes a deal there,
‪she'd only have time to sign an MOU.
‪It's quite an odd move.
‪Have our people look into it.
‪This is the list of attendees
‪for the Singapore conference.
‪The sole agenda of the upcoming
‪general meeting is her removal,
‪yet she's traveling abroad for business?
‪Compile a list of shareholders
‪who recently transferred their shares.
‪Yes, sir.
‪I'm too worried about you
‪going abroad on your own.
‪There's nothing to worry about.
‪I'll be just fine.
‪No, not about you.
‪I'm worried about myself.
‪I'm already dreading the thought
‪of not seeing you for days.
‪Then come with me.
‪Don't prosecutors go abroad
‪on business trips?
‪There are global seminars and conferences.
‪Should I actually look into it?
‪Leave it. I won't be away for long.
‪Okay.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪I'll come to the airport to see you off.
‪Man, I barely finished it in time.
‪Hold on.
‪There's more?
‪Silly me.
‪-You should've handed it over earlier.
‪-Mr. Ma.
‪What's all that?
‪The Case Division assigned us some cases.
‪Why today, of all days…
‪Oh, man.
‪Come on!
‪Why are there so many?
‪Ms. Eom is already there
‪and arranging meetings on her end.
‪I'll keep you updated
‪if anything needs to be arranged
‪on this end.
‪Take good care of my grandmother
‪until I come back.
‪Please don't worry.
‪Remember, I'm Bong Ji-uk.
‪Ma'am.
‪Good luck.
‪Thank you.
‪Of course.
‪-Yeo-ri.
‪-Oh.
‪-Gang-uk.
‪-Hello.
‪Hello.
‪-Mr. Bong, wait.
‪-Yes?
‪Oh, dear. Sorry.
‪Weren't you busy with work?
‪Don't worry about my work.
‪I'd take you to Singapore if I could.
‪Huh?
‪What's going on?
‪Why? What is it?
‪Is Kang Min-hwan going too?
‪I didn't know he was going.
‪Should I go too?
‪I think I should come with you.
‪Don't be silly.
‪I'll be fine.
‪Call me if something happens, okay?
‪I'll fly right over to see you.
‪Promise me, okay?
‪Sure.
‪-Hyeong-min, that thing from last time.
‪-What?
‪Is this year's International Association
‪of Prosecutors event in Singapore?
‪It has to be, okay? Pull up the notice.
‪-Yeah, that one.
‪-It is happening in Singapore.
‪"Prosecution organizations
‪and personnel from around the world
‪gather to discuss
‪ideal criminal legislation."
‪It's open to well-rounded prosecutors.
‪That's me. This is perfect.
‪Sign me up immediately.
‪Forget it.
‪Don't even dream of going abroad.
‪You refused to go because
‪you didn't want to write an extra report.
‪No, not anymore.
‪I'll write up a killer report.
‪Hyeong-min, sign me up right now.
‪-I can't.
‪-What?
‪Applications were due yesterday.
‪There's a conference in Thailand
‪to review international law.
‪Yes, there is.
‪Call up the organization hosting that
‪and have them host it
‪in Singapore instead, okay?
‪What?
‪Let's say they move it to Singapore
‪and all you have to do is go.
‪But today is your turn
‪to handle the night shift.
‪You forgot?
‪Oh, jeez.
‪You forgot.
‪Let's go, sir.
‪Will you attend the reception later?
‪Most of the investors will be there.
‪Of course. I'll be there.
‪Hello?
‪Ma'am, I just heard from Ms. Han.
‪She wants to meet you an hour later.
‪Did she say why?
‪I asked, but she only said
‪it was personal.
‪I didn't want to upset her
‪before negotiations,
‪so I said you'd agree to the delay.
‪I apologize.
‪I understand. Bye.
‪Are you Ms. Cheon?
‪Hello, Ms. Han.
‪I was surprised to get your call.
‪You came all the way here
‪to meet me over my 3% stake?
‪I wanted to meet you in person.
‪I did some research myself.
‪Some want you removed
‪because of your scandals
‪and poor management skills.
‪I can't say I've been perfect
‪at every turn,
‪but I can't accept the claim
‪that I mismanaged the company
‪enough to warrant a removal motion.
‪I can prove it with objective numbers.
‪Would you take a look?
‪I'll be honest with you.
‪The truth is,
‪someone made me a bold offer
‪just an hour ago.
‪They offered double
‪the current market price for my shares.
‪-They offered double?
‪-So I agreed to transfer them.
‪What?
‪Was it one of Director Ok's people?
‪No.
‪I have to keep their identity undisclosed
‪until the deal is signed.
‪From my perspective,
‪I have no reason to turn down the offer.
‪Ms. Han.
‪From what I see,
‪it's just a mudslinging fight
‪between family members.
‪Doesn't it all end up the same,
‪whoever becomes CEO?
‪You must know how things are, Ms. Han.
‪Fights like these.
‪You went through a legal dispute
‪with your younger brother.
‪Let's leave my family out of this
‪when it's about yours.
‪To be truthful, I have no interest
‪in your fight to defend your position.
‪I'm busy enough
‪running my own business here.
‪I'm here for your business
‪interests as well.
‪I don't see you
‪as a mere shareholder
‪or someone whose shares I need to acquire.
‪I want us to build our careers together
‪through our shared passion for art.
‪If you side with me this time,
‪I'll give you the right to curate
‪and host exhibitions anywhere you want.
‪That includes both
‪Reina's domestic and overseas affiliates.
‪With such authority,
‪you may not be able to
‪double your investment right away,
‪but the profit you stand to gain
‪in a few years will be much greater.
‪That is a very alluring offer.
‪It could boost my career too.
‪But I care more about my immediate reality
‪than the distant future.
‪Thank you for the offer,
‪but I'll have to decline.
‪-Ms. Han.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪Just a moment.
‪Can you hear me out a little more
‪before you make up your mind?
‪Well, I've already made up my mind.
‪I don't think talking any further
‪will change anything.
‪But still…
‪Are you all right, ma'am?
‪Find out if Ms. Han will
‪attend the reception tonight.
‪I already checked.
‪Her name is on the list.
‪Are you all right?
‪I heard your company's struggling.
‪The company is fine.
‪I'm the one struggling.
‪That's why I came all this way.
‪I'm sure you'll manage.
‪You're Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪Apparently, it's some kind of
‪mystical object.
‪Ji-hwan!
‪You have to live.
‪I'll die instead.
‪12 YEARS AGO
‪Hold this for me.
‪Oh, come on. In this day and age,
‪you really think wearing that
‪will keep ghosts away?
‪Look. My grandma said something
‪about this pendant.
‪Apparently, it's some kind of
‪mystical object.
‪Hey, I'm being serious.
‪My grandma acts like
‪it's the end of the world
‪if I so much as take it off.
‪Well, it's not like
‪there's no way to confirm it.
‪I believe you.
‪Why don't you try wearing it?
‪-Me?
‪-I have a feeling
‪it'll suit you way better than me.
‪You know, necklaces like this
‪look better when worn by someone pretty.
‪It looks great on you.
‪You can keep it.
‪Really?
‪But what if something happens to you?
‪That's just my luck then.
‪I don't mind it
‪if it means I can save you.
‪-What?
‪-If something does happen,
‪you have to live. I'll die instead.
‪Why would you say something like that?
‪Are you okay? Oh, jeez.
‪Wait here.
‪I'll get something to wipe you dry.
‪Okay.
‪Is something wrong?
‪Let me see…
‪-Do we have any tissues?
‪-Tissues?
‪I don't know. I don't see any.
‪There aren't any here.
‪Ji-hwan!
‪Yeo-ri!
‪What if something happens to you?
‪I don't mind it
‪if it means I can save you.
‪If something does happen,
‪you have to live. I'll die instead.
‪The pendant.
‪Are you okay?
‪Yeah.
‪I'd forgotten…
‪a lot of the memories from back then.
‪Do you remember Ji-hwan's pendant
‪from the accident 12 years ago?
‪What pendant?
‪The necklace.
‪Ji-hwan put it on me that day.
‪I was wearing it.
‪Do you know if it was
‪among his belongings?
‪I'm not sure.
‪If you were wearing it,
‪maybe you lost it
‪when you fell into the sea?
‪Did I?
‪Ma'am.
‪Excuse me.
‪It's about Ms. Han.
‪She checked out of the hotel
‪30 minutes before this reception.
‪What?
‪Let's go.
‪Ms. Cheon was in continued contact
‪with a woman named Han Se-in in Singapore.
‪CKO CONSTRUCTION, HAN SE-IN, NEUTRAL
‪She owns exactly 3%.
‪I'm quite surprised and also flustered.
‪You're offering double the market price?
‪A card has the greatest impact
‪when it's played
‪at the most unexpected moment.
‪That is true.
‪So is this the reason
‪you asked me to delay my meeting
‪with Ms. Cheon by an hour?
‪A deal is best when offered first.
‪I have just one condition.
‪Until the deal is finalized,
‪you are to keep
‪the buyer's identity undisclosed.
‪That's all I ask.
‪Have you called her?
‪She's not answering.
‪I think she's avoiding the calls.
‪First, call Mr. Bong.
‪Tell him to put a team together
‪and find out what Ms. Han is up to.
‪Yes, ma'am.
‪Wait a minute.
‪Ms. Han has nothing to do
‪with hotel investment.
‪Yet she was invited to this event.
‪I'll look into who invited her here.
‪I love this.
‪Is this much okay?
‪Man, it's not here. Where is it?
‪What's this?
‪He never said a word to me.
‪Give me that.
‪Why do you have this?
‪-Do you…
‪-It's not like that.
‪What do you mean?
‪Min-hwan.
‪Have you lied to me all along?
‪What did I lie about?
‪You asked me if I'd asked Yeo-ri out.
‪You said the matching rings were too much.
‪You lied whenever I asked
‪because you had an ulterior motive.
‪I didn't lie about anything.
‪And I don't have to explain
‪my feelings to you.
‪I don't want to argue with you about this.
‪That's your problem.
‪If there's something wrong, talk about it.
‪Why do you always avoid the situation?
‪Min-hwan.
‪Min-hwan!
‪Kang Min-hwan.
‪Want me to tell you
‪why I avoid the situation?
‪I can argue with you about anything,
‪but nothing will change.
‪What won't change?
‪If I so much as raise my voice at you,
‪do you know how our family looks at me?
‪What do you mean?
‪Tell me. How do they look at you?
‪Forget it. I've had enough.
‪Do you have some kind of victim mentality?
‪What?
‪What's wrong?
‪It's still a zero-sum game.
‪If we take shares from them,
‪they take shares from us.
‪We still don't know
‪what Ms. Han is up to, do we?
‪Yes.
‪Keep looking into it.
‪Bye.
‪INCOMING CALL
‪Hello? Yeo-ri?
‪You're still awake.
‪I was worried you'd be asleep.
‪I wouldn't be asleep.
‪How are things going on your end?
‪Not too well, to be honest.
‪She turned me down at our first meeting,
‪and she's been ignoring us since then.
‪She left without a trace.
‪Man, that's not good.
‪You must've been flustered.
‪Which is why, Gang-uk,
‪I need to ask for a favor.
‪I gave it a lot of thought
‪before calling you.
‪Of course, tell me what you need.
‪I'll help with anything.
‪First, there's something
‪I'd like you to pass to my secretary.
‪-Okay.
‪-And the other favor is…
‪Could you help us locate Han Se-in?
‪I do have a team looking for her,
‪but we're short on time.
‪I can totally do that.
‪I know a guy
‪whose specialty is finding people.
‪I'll call him right away.
‪Thank--
‪What's this about?
‪Hyeong-min,
‪I'm all sorts of urgent right now.
‪I racked my brain
‪and you're the only one I could think of.
‪What do you want me to do?
‪-No way. I won't do it.
‪-Come on.
‪From the sushi restaurant nearby
‪that you love so much,
‪I brought an assortment
‪of the freshest-looking sushi.
‪Look.
‪-Mr. Ma, what do you take me for?
‪-Yeah?
‪Do you think
‪a few pieces of sushi would…
‪-Shall I have a taste?
‪-Yeah. Sit down.
‪-Is this it?
‪-Yeah, that's it.
‪BREATHING NEW LIFE INTO OLD PAINTINGS
‪Here, open wide.
‪Okay.
‪Want the eel next?
‪Here.
‪-She was in Singapore until recently.
‪-Okay.
‪The photos on her social media
‪show the exhibition venues
‪and the art she handled.
‪-This lady, though.
‪-Yeah?
‪She must have a personal account
‪aside from this official one.
‪You think so?
‪Hold on.
‪Here, open up.
‪-Here? Or lower?
‪-Yes, there.
‪-No, that side.
‪-This side?
‪Your muscles are so tense.
‪It's illegal to look up
‪one's credit card transactions.
‪There's a limit to what I can find
‪on social media alone.
‪Hyeong-min, that's exactly why
‪I came to you for help.
‪On to your right shoulder.
‪My gosh, this side is even worse.
‪Mr. Ma.
‪-Mr. Ma.
‪-Huh?
‪Take a look at this.
‪The same photo
‪keeps appearing on her feed.
‪She seems to post it
‪whenever it comes to mind.
‪Take a look.
‪This place is…
‪What time is it?
‪I need to call that elder.
‪Madam Pang?
‪-Hyeong-min, I have a flight to catch.
‪-Okay.
‪-Call me when you have something, okay?
‪-What?
‪Thanks a lot.
‪Clean up after yourself. I love you.
‪Mr. Ma.
‪You punk.
‪He got me again.
‪Thank you.
‪Hello, Mr. Bong.
‪I just got it. All right.
‪He's not there either?
‪Okay then.
‪I understand. Okay, bye.
‪If he's not in Ms. Im's office,
‪he's not in the building.
‪Where else could he be? His grandmother's?
‪No, she seemed clueless.
‪He's never been late for work.
‪It's eleven o'clock now, so where is he?
‪Where on earth is he? Why--
‪-Ma Gang-uk, this punk…
‪-Sir.
‪He's over at…
‪He went to Mr. Hwang's office.
‪What are you on about?
‪That's where I'm coming from.
‪-You see, Ma--
‪-Yes. He was there,
‪then he went to the bathroom.
‪The men's, of course.
‪He had a stomachache this morning.
‪If it's urgent, I'll pass it to him
‪-in the bath--
‪-What's with you?
‪That punk called me at the crack of dawn
‪and said he needed to take three days off.
‪He just does whatever he pleases.
‪Is something going on?
‪-You don't know, do you?
‪-Well…
‪I signed it, so process it.
‪That troublemaker.
‪LEAVE REQUEST: MA GANG-UK
‪He took three days off.
‪Why didn't he tell us? Where did he go?
‪He went to Singapore.
‪He actually went?
‪After all that fuss, he actually went?
‪What on earth is going on?
‪Why didn't you tell me anything?
‪I figured if I knew,
‪there was no way you didn't…
‪I thought you'd know. I'm sorry.
‪I stayed up working on something
‪with Mr. Ma,
‪so I was a bit out of it this morning.
‪You two stayed up last night without me?
‪Yes.
‪How come? Why wasn't I there?
‪Why wasn't I included?
‪That's not fair. I'm hurt.
‪Why would you feel hurt?
‪You should be glad
‪you didn't have to suffer
‪and stay up working.
‪We only ate spicy rice cakes. That's it.
‪Man, I'm tired.
‪I saw traces of sushi.
‪We had pizza too.
‪I saw you had blood sausage too.
‪-I swear I cleaned up.
‪-Darn you.
‪-How could you?
‪-Okay. I'll treat you.
‪I'll kill you if I catch you again.
‪Goodness, Yeo-ri is all you talk about.
‪Does she know you're like this?
‪I might tell her on this trip.
‪Yes, hello.
‪I'd like to see you.
‪Ma'am.
‪A private investor called Danny Tan
‪invited Ms. Han.
‪I just arranged a meeting with him.
‪-Is that so?
‪-Yes.
‪He wants to meet you
‪at the aquarium at 3 p.m.
‪Okay. Good work.
‪It's lovely here,
‪whatever time of year I visit.
‪I love it here as well.
‪The view is extra special today.
‪And the tea tastes even better
‪with you here, Ms. Song.
‪Take a nice walk around the grounds,
‪and stay for dinner as well.
‪Is Mr. Ma doing well?
‪I only saw him from afar,
‪but he seemed to be doing well.
‪He's so busy with work.
‪I got a call from him
‪the day after the ceremony
‪and nothing since.
‪Actually, I asked to see you because…
‪Yes, of course. I'm listening.
‪Well…
‪Could you arrange for me
‪to meet Mr. Ma over a meal?
‪You can introduce me
‪as a close acquaintance.
‪Yes, of course. I can do that.
‪I'll arrange something,
‪then call you right away.
‪By the way,
‪you said you're well-acquainted
‪with his fiancée's grandmother.
‪We're in the same field,
‪as you already know.
‪Yeo-ri and Ji-hwan were friends
‪since they were young,
‪and they went to the same school too.
‪Oh, they were friends?
‪They're not the same age, are they?
‪Ji-hwan was born
‪in the year of the monkey,
‪and Yeo-ri was born
‪in the year of the goat.
‪That can't be.
‪Yeo-ri and Ji-hwan are the same age.
‪Whose is this?
‪MAY 8, 1991, 18:00
‪FEMALE, YEAR OF THE GOAT
‪Could it be…
‪No need for excuses.
‪That date and time of birth.
‪Who does it really belong to?
‪Oh, right. This…
‪This is my wife's date of birth.
‪You see…
‪Okay. I'm really sorry.
‪What am I to do with that punk?
‪Perhaps I could explain…
‪Make an excuse?
‪I wouldn't call it an excuse.
‪Gang-uk was really stressed out over this,
‪and he kept letting out deep sighs.
‪Since I'm older than him,
‪I wanted to help him out.
‪For their love, their true love…
‪Enough.
‪So,
‪where is Gang-uk right now?
‪Hello?
‪Ma'am, it's about Danny Tan.
‪He called to say he had to attend
‪another urgent meeting.
‪What should I do?
‪All right. Bye.
‪Gang-uk.
‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪I missed you so much, Yeo-ri.
‪I'm glad you're here with me.
‪-Cheers.
‪Want to come in for a cup of tea?
‪How can I be sure that my 3%
‪will be enough for you to win?
‪You're desperate.
‪Don't you want to protect it?
‪We will now begin the extraordinary
‪general meeting of shareholders
‪regarding the motion for removal
‪of Reina Hotel's CEO, Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪Then Cheon Yeo-ri will
‪no longer have a hold on Reina.
‪Ma Gang-uk, was it?
‪Is he giving you trouble?
‪What's going on here?
‪You've been reassigned
‪to an overseas training program.
‪Gang-uk is
‪going abroad?
‪Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim